###### POWERFUL FLEXIBLE TECHNOLOGY

* [AppDiscovery
    
    Acquire your ideal users](https://www.applovin.com/appdiscovery/)
* [MAX
    
    Monetize your app](https://www.applovin.com/max/)
* [SparkLabs
    
    Create ads that perform](https://www.applovin.com/sparklabs/)
* [AppLovin Exchange
    
    Reach your audience](https://www.applovin.com/alx/)
* [Array
    
    Increase value across customer’s lifecycle](https://www.applovin.com/array/)
* [Adjust
    
    Measure your marketing](https://www.applovin.com/adjust/)
* [Wurl
    
    Take control of your CTV strategy](https://www.applovin.com/wurl/)

###### SOLUTIONS FOR YOUR GOALS

###### Resource Center

###### Featured posts

[

###### New Report: Consumer Mobile Trends 2024](https://www.applovin.com/reports/consumer-mobile-trends-marketing-channel-diversification/)

[

###### New Webinar: Metaplay & Gamification](https://www.applovin.com/blog/new-interactive-ads-webinar-about-metaplay-and-gamification-is-live/)

###### More about us

Privacy Policy
==============

###### [Overview](https://www.applovin.com/policies)

###### Policies

###### Terms

**Effective Date**: September 13, 2024  
You can find the prior version [here](https://www.applovin.com/privacy-prior/).

AppLovin Corporation (“we,” “us,” “our,” or “AppLovin”) operates a suite of tools for app developers and other businesses to automate and optimize the marketing and monetization of their platforms, products, or services by enabling the placement of different types of advertisements on digital properties including mobile apps, websites, and connected TV devices (collectively, the “Advertising Services” or “Services”).  As explained below, consumers interact with us in a few ways, primarily through advertisements served by AppLovin on behalf of advertisers.

The AppLovin Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”) explains how we collect, use, and share information through our Services and advertising platform, and our corporate website at www.applovin.com (the “Website”), as well as your choices related to that information.

### Contents

Our Advertising Services
------------------------

This section describes the information we collect, use, and share through our Advertising Services.

### General Information Collection and Use

If you are a consumer who downloads and uses an application which contains the AppLovin SDK or otherwise interacts with the Services through advertisements served within a digital property, we may collect certain information, including the following:

**Device, App, and Browser Data**

* Device make, model, and operating system;
* Device properties related to screen size, orientation, audio, battery, device memory usage, settings, and boot time;
* Device settings related to accessibility features, font size, and theme; 
* Carrier;
* Name and properties of mobile application through which a consumer interacts with the Services;
* Country, time zone, and locale settings (country and preferred language);
* Network connection type and speed;
* IP Address;
* Internet browser user-agent used to access the Services;
* HTTP header information;
* Advertising IDs (IDFA/GAID/Amazon FOSAID);
* Vendor IDs (IDFV);
* App Set IDs; and
* Advertising and tracking preferences and restrictions.

Application publishers may choose to share with us additional information including your age or year of birth, gender, email, phone number, and interest segments for purposes of their own direct ad serving.  We do not retain this data or pass it downstream to advertising partners.  Please see the applicable publisher’s privacy policy for more information about their use of first party data.

Advertisers (through the advertiser itself or through a third party service provider on behalf of such advertiser) may also share transactional or “event” data related to a consumer’s interaction with an application, such as information about the actions taken in an application like purchases or application installations.

**Information Collection and Use Specific** **to** **e-Commerce Ads Only**

If you are a consumer who interacts with the Services through an e-commerce platform or a merchant website, we may collect certain additional information (that you provided to the e-commerce platform or merchant, through a third party’s API, our SDK, pixel, or other similar technologies), including the following:

**Personal Identifiers** 

* Names;
* Email addresses;
* Phone numbers;
* Mailing addresses; and
* Usernames.

**Shopping and Browsing Data and Events** 

* Shopping browsing behavior (e.g., views) and search history;
* Records of products purchased or considered (e.g., added to cart, check out);
* Purchasing histories; 
* Tendencies or preferences; and
* Information regarding user interactions with advertising partners and their merchant partners’ sites and advertisements.

**How We Collect Your Information**

This information may be collected automatically across mobile apps and devices or received from third-parties across different technologies over time. We may also combine information we collect with other information we derive through analytical techniques, and we will use that combined information to offer the Services. 

**How We Use Your Information**

We generally use the information we collect to:

* Deliver the Services, maintain, and improve them, including our AI-powered advertising technology, and research and develop new ones;
* Promote safety, security, and integrity of Services;
* Provide measurement, analytics, and reporting; and
* Comply with legal and regulatory obligations.

We use AI-powered advertising technology (sometimes referred to as “automated decision-making”) to help us improve our advertising products and Services and serve ads that are relevant and interesting to you. We use it in ways that do not produce legal or similarly significant effects on you (for example, by reordering how advertisements might appear when you visit a digital property such as a mobile app or a website).

### Information Sharing

We may share information we collect or derive with third parties in the following contexts:

* **Service Providers.** We transfer information to service providers, and other partners who support our business, such as providing technical infrastructure services, analyzing how our Services are used, measuring the effectiveness of ads and services, providing customer service, or facilitating payments. These partners must adhere to strict confidentiality obligations in a way that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the agreements we enter into with them.
* **Affiliates.** We may share information within the AppLovin family of companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
* **Advertising Partners.** We share information with our third-party advertising partners, including advertisers, ad networks, exchanges, demand side platforms, merchants, other advertising partners (who aggregate their own demand sources), and ad optimization and measurement/attribution partners (e.g., mobile measurement partners or “MMPs”) to provide our clients with Advertising Services. This information may be used by such third-party partners to measure how effective ads are, show advertisements to end users for products and services that are more likely to appeal to them (a practice known as interest-based advertising or behavioral advertising), and to undertake web analytics to analyze traffic and other ad activity to improve the advertising experience.  
      
    Unless otherwise noted in our partner list, each AppLovin advertising partner is an independent controller of your data. You can view a list of AppLovin advertising partners with whom we share your data [here](https://www.applovin.com/applovin-partners-privacy/), current as of the date listed at the top of that page.  
      
    If you do not want to receive interest-based advertisements, please see the [“Manage Your Privacy Choices”](https://www.applovin.com/privacy/#manage-privacy) section below. If you are located in the European Union, UK, or Switzerland, you may also see the [“Additional Provisions for EU/UK/Swiss Individuals”](https://www.applovin.com/privacy/#specific-provisions-eu) section below for more options. If you are an individual resident of the U.S. states that have enacted comprehensive consumer privacy laws, you may also review the “[U.S. Multistate Privacy Notice](https://www.applovin.com/privacy/#specific-provisions)” section below for more options.  
      
    Please note that the practices of our third-party advertising partners delivering advertisements through our Services are subject to those partners’ own privacy policies.
* **Regulatory or Legal Requirements.** We may disclose information to governmental regulatory authorities as required by law, including for tax or accounting purposes, in response to their requests for such information or to assist in investigations. We may also disclose personal information to third parties in connection with claims, disputes, or litigation, when otherwise required by law or court order.
* **Safety and Terms Enforcement.** We may disclose information if we determine, in our sole discretion, that its disclosure is necessary to protect the health, safety, or rights of you or any other person, protect against fraud, or enforce our legal rights, including contractual commitments made to us by third parties.
* **Business Transfers.** We may disclose personal information as part of an organizational business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, joint venture, financing, or sale of organizational assets and may transfer personal information to a third party as one of the business assets in such a transaction. We may also disclose personal information in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership.

### Manage Your Privacy Choices:

To limit collection of information from mobile devices, please visit your device’s settings to set the “Limit Ad Track” or other similar features on your device. Additionally, you may opt-out of interest-based advertising within ads served by AppLovin. For detailed instructions, see [How AppLovin Shows You Ads](https://dash.applovin.com/p/how-applovin-shows-you-ads). You can also make choices about data collection for certain companies by visiting an industry consumer choice platform such as the NAI ([https://optout.networkadvertising.org/](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/)) or DAA ([https://optout.aboutads.info/](https://optout.aboutads.info/)).  You may still receive ads after limiting processing of information for interest-based advertising, but those ads may be less relevant to your interests. 

To see or manage the data collected by AppLovin from your device, you may download the AppLovin Privacy Management Application from the Apple or Google Play Stores:

By navigating through the tabs in the AppLovin Privacy Management Application, you can erase the personal information that AppLovin may have collected about you or request a copy of that personal information.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from, or serve advertisements to, children as defined and required by applicable laws. If you believe we have served an advertisement to a child or might have any personal information from or about a child, or if you believe a mobile application in which an AppLovin-served advertisement appeared may be designed for, directed to, or pass personal information knowingly from, children in violation of our policies, please contact us via email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.applovin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Data Security and Retention

We implement reasonable measures to help secure the information we collect through the Services. We retain the data we collect through the Services for up to 2 years. Information is automatically purged from our system if the Services do not receive any updated information for a device in the last 2 years. Note that we will retain information in our systems for as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

\[END OF ADVERTISING SERVICES-SPECIFIC PROVISIONS\]

Our Website
-----------

This section describes the information we collect, use, and share through our Website.

### **Cookies and Other Similar Technology**

The Website uses cookies, web beacons, or other similar technology to collect information for various purposes, including interest-based advertising. This information may include your IP address, device identifier, browser type, device type, the date and time of your visit, and the areas of the Website you visit. To learn more about and manage the cookies on this Website, please click “Cookie Settings” in our Website footer. You may also be able to limit the use of cookies through your browser settings. Note that certain parts of the Website may not function properly without cookies. Additionally, you may still receive ads after limiting processing of information for interest-based advertising, but those ads may be less relevant to your interests. If you erase your cookies, reset your device identifier, or use different browsers or devices, you may need to make your choices again.

We partner with Google Analytics to learn more about how you use our Website. For more information about how Google Analytics works you can visit [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/12159447?hl=en). To opt-out of Google Analytics, you can visit [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) and follow the instructions.  

### **Additional Information Collection for Business Account Owners**

When you register with AppLovin to use our Services, you may provide us with personal information such as your name, email address, phone number, mailing address, user name, and password. You may also provide us with payment information when you submit or receive a payment, or other information when you complete the online forms available on the Website. We may also acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information that you voluntarily provide to us or that we collect automatically.

### **How We Use Your Information**

We may use the information we collect or you provide to us through the Website for various purposes, including:

* To communicate with you, for example through newsletters or with other information about our products and services;
* To operate and improve the Website and our Services;
* To customize the Website;
* For analytics and research;
* For marketing purposes; and
* For purposes disclosed at the time of collection.

### Information Sharing

We may share information we collect through the Website in the following contexts:

* With your consent;
* For advertising and marketing purposes;
* In response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process;
* To protect our rights and the rights of others;
* With our affiliates;
* With service providers that help us operate the Website and Services;
* As part of a sale, merger, or acquisition, including at bankruptcy; and
* For purposes disclosed at the time of collection.

### Links to Other Websites

The Website may provide links to other websites or other digital properties that we do not control. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of those digital properties that you may visit.

### Updating Information

You can update the personal information you provide to us by correcting, updating, or deleting the information associated with you via your AppLovin account. To add, modify, remove, or request access to the personal information about you that we hold, please see the [“Contact Us”](#contact-us) section below.

### Your Marketing Choices

If you no longer wish to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt out of receiving these emails by clicking “Unsubscribe” at the bottom of any marketing email you receive from us or by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.applovin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Children

Our Website is not intended for use by children as defined and required by applicable law. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children through the Website. If you believe we might have any personal information from or about a child, please contact us via email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.applovin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Data Security and Retention

We have implemented reasonable physical, technical, and administrative security measures for the Website to help protect information we collect and store.

For detailed information regarding retention associated with cookies on the applovin.com domain, please click “Cookie Settings” in our Website footer to learn more. 

We retain other information such as customer contact and payment information in our systems for as long as necessary as permitted by law to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

\[END OF WEBSITE-SPECIFIC PROVISIONS\]

Additional Provisions for EU/UK/Swiss Individuals
-------------------------------------------------

If you are located in the European Union, United Kingdom, or Switzerland, the following additional provisions apply to you.

### **Data Privacy Framework**

AppLovin complies with the EU-U.S Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce.

AppLovin has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF.  AppLovin has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

If you are an EU, UK, or Swiss individual, where we transfer your personal data to third party servicer providers (see above) who perform services for us or on our behalf, we are responsible for the processing of that data by them and shall remain liable if they process your personal data in a manner inconsistent with the DPF Principles, unless we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. 

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Data Privacy Framework, AppLovin is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, AppLovin may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, AppLovin commits to resolve DPF Principles-related complaints about our collection and use of your personal information. EU, UK, and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF should first contact AppLovin at [\[email protected\]](https://www.applovin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). AppLovin refers unresolved complaints to TRUSTe, an alternative dispute resolution provider based in the United States.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your DPF Principles-related complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your DPF Principles-related complaint to your satisfaction, please visit [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) for more information or to file a complaint.  These dispute resolution services are provided at no cost to you.

For complaints regarding DPF compliance not resolved by any of the other DPF mechanisms, you have the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration. Further information can be found on the official DPF website.

### Lawful Basis for Processing

On certain occasions, we process your personal data when it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party, such as to provide services to you. We may also process your personal data to respond to your inquiries concerning our products and services.

On other occasions, we process your personal data where required by law. We may also process your personal data if necessary to protect your interests or the interests of a third party.

Additionally, we process your personal data when necessary to do so for fraud prevention, improving our network and services, and marketing our services to advertisers and publishers, where these interests are not overridden by your data protection rights.

If the processing of your personal data is necessary, we will generally ensure that consent has been obtained from you if there is no other lawful basis for such processing. You have the right to withdraw your consent to processing of personal data at any time.

If personal data covered by this Privacy Policy is to be used for a new purpose that is materially different from that for which the personal data was originally collected or subsequently authorized, or is to be disclosed to a non-agent third party in a manner not specified in this Privacy Policy, we will provide you with an opportunity to choose whether to have your personal data so used or disclosed. Requests to opt out of such uses or disclosures of personal data should be sent to us as specified in the “Contact” section below. Certain personal data, such as information about medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, is considered “Sensitive Information”. AppLovin does not collect or seek to elicit “Sensitive Information”.

For questions about data processing, please contact our Data Protection Officer. Visit the “Contact” section below for contact information.

### Your Rights

**If you are an individual in the EU, UK, or Switzerland, you are able:**

* To request access to the personal data we hold about you;
* To request that we rectify or erase your personal data;
* To request that we restrict or block the processing of your personal data;
* Under certain circumstances, to receive personal data about you that we store and transmit to another without hindrance from us, including requesting that we provide your personal data directly to another, i.e., a right to data portability; and
* Where we previously obtained your consent, to withdraw consent to processing your personal data.

To exercise these rights, please contact us at the email address set forth in the [“Contact Us”](https://www.applovin.com/privacy/#contact-us) section below.  Our Data Protection Officer can also be reached at this email address.  Please be aware that we may be unable to afford these rights to you under certain circumstances, such as if we are legally prevented from doing so.

In certain circumstances, you may appoint an authorized agent to exercise any rights that you may have on your behalf.  If you choose to exercise any rights through an authorized agent, you will need to verify your identity directly with us before we can process any requests.  In addition, we will need written documentation demonstrating the authorized agent’s authority to act on your behalf.

Additionally, you have the right to lodge a complaint against us. To do so, contact the supervisory authority in your country of residence.

**EU and UK Privacy Representatives**

We have appointed [Prighter Group](https://prighter.com/) as our privacy representatives in the EU and UK.  You can contact us through our privacy representatives at the following addresses:

_For residents of the EU_:**  
PrighterGDPR-Rep by Maetzler Rechtsanwalts GmbH & Co KG  
**c/o AppLovin Corporation  
Kriegerstraße 44  
30161 Hannover  
Germany  
  
_For residents of the UK_:  
**PrighterUK-Rep by Prighter Ltd.**  
c/o AppLovin Corporation  
20 Mortlake Mortlake High Street  
London, SW14 8JN  
United Kingdom

Additional information regarding our privacy representatives can be found at the following link: [https://prighter.com/q/19826057144](https://prighter.com/q/19826057144).

\[END OF EU/UK/SWISS SPECIFIC PROVISIONS\]

U.S. Multistate Privacy Notice
------------------------------

Additional provisions for individual residents of the U.S. states that have enacted comprehensive consumer privacy laws are included in our [U.S. Multistate Privacy Notice](https://www.applovin.com/multistate-privacy-notice/), which explains how those residents may exercise their privacy rights.

Policy Changes
--------------

We may, in our sole discretion, make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements, or for other purposes. If we make any changes, we will update the “Effective Date” posted at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes, we may notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you understand how we collect, use, and share information.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Website. By continuing to use the Website or Advertising Services following such changes, you are agreeing to accept the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please write to us at:

Data Protection Officer  
AppLovin Corporation  
1100 Page Mill Road  
Palo Alto, CA 94304

You can also contact us or our Data Protection Officer via email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.applovin.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Please be sure to include your relevant account information in any correspondence to us.  This will help ensure that we can respond to your inquiry in a timely manner.

If you have a customer care issue, please visit [AppLovin Support](https://support.applovin.com/).

###### PRODUCTS

###### SOLUTIONS

###### RESOURCES

###### ABOUT US

###### INSIDE APPLOVIN

Copyright © 2024 AppLovin. All rights reserved.

[Your Privacy Choices](https://www.applovin.com/multistate-privacy-notice/) Cookie Settings

    * [AppDiscovery
        
        The growth engine for your apps](https://www.applovin.com/appdiscovery/)
    * [MAX
        
        A better way to monetize your app](https://www.applovin.com/max/)
    * [AppLovin Exchange
        
        Reach your audience](https://www.applovin.com/alx/)
    * [Array
        
        Maximize your opportunity](https://www.applovin.com/array/)
    * [SparkLabs
        
        Creatives to drive results](https://www.applovin.com/sparklabs/)
    * [Adjust
        
        Measure your marketing](https://www.applovin.com/adjust/)
    * [Wurl
        
        A powerful platform for CTV streaming](https://www.applovin.com/wurl/)

Resources

Company
